Narrator: A
Speaker: Yes, I have. I drive a lot in my job, several hours a day,
and I like listening to books – it’s much better than listening to the radio.
I probably listen to a couple of books every week.
Narrator: B
Speaker: Yes, I’ve seen The Lord of the Rings films at least ten times.
They’re really great films, I never get tired of them, I always notice something new.
Narrator: C
Speaker: Yes, I’ve definitely fallen asleep watching a film on TV,
but never in the cinema.
Narrator: D
Speaker: Yes, I have. At Christmas last year, I watched the complete season four
of Stranger Things in one evening.
Narrator: E
Speaker: No, I haven’t. It usually takes me a long time to finish a book,
so I never read them again.
Narrator: F
Speaker: Yes, I loved Encanto, you know, the Disney film,
so I downloaded the soundtrack.
It’s got some great songs, by lots of different singers.